Memorabilia Collection, 1782-2011 (bulk 1866-1997): Finding Aid AC053
University Archives
- Series 8: Medals, 1765-2010; 12 boxes
  - Reunion medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Silver with Princeton seal; black ribbon.
  - Reunion medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold, Princeton seal in orange and black; black ribbon; bronze tag engraved "Princeton 1907."
  - Silver medal, 1909; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Silver and round; seal of Georgetown University, "Georgetown University Athletic Association" engraved on front; "50 Meters Invitation 1909" engraved on back.
  - Silver medal, 1909; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Silver and round; seal of Georgetown University, "Georgetown University Athletic Association" engraved on front; "50 Meters Handicap 1909" engraved on back.
  - Silver medal, 1909; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Silver and round; seals of Princeton and of Yale, "Princeton-Yale University Track A. A." engraved on front; "100 Yds Dash 1909" engraved on back.
  - Silver medal, 1937; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Silver and rectangular; a man readying for dash engraved on front; "2nd high Jump 1937" engraved on back.
  - Silver medal, circa 1937; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Silver and round; a tiger, "Intramural," "Athletic Association" engraved on front; "Championship 1937-38," "X-Country Upperclass P. B. Applegate" engraved on back.
  - Silver medal, 1938; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Silver and round; a woman on wings and with olive branches in hands, "New Jersey Association Championship" engraved on front; "1938 2nd Relay" engraved on back.
  - Silver medal, 1952; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Silver and round with a man. "Le Roy N. Mills Memorial Trophy Medal" engraved on front; "Presented by the Class of 1905 of Princeton University 1952," and Princeton seal engraved on back; orange and black ribbon.
  - Silver medal, 1905; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Silver with a foot on wings, "JHU," "Athletic 1905 Meet" engraved on front; "2nd Prize 440 Yd Run Interscholastic Won by R. A. Gamble" engraved on back.
  - Silver medal, 1906; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Silver with "P" in orange and black, "Annual Indoor Athletic Meet 1906" engraved on front; 50 Yds Dash Ralph A. Gamble. March 23" engraved on back.
  - Silver medal, 1906; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Silver with "P" in orange and black, "Caledonian Games P. U. T. A. A." engraved on front; "220 Yds Run 1906 Ralph A. Gamble April 24" engraved on back.
  - Silver medal, 1907; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Silver with a man throwing, "Jamestown Exposition College Championship 1907" engraved on front; "220 Yds Hurdle" engraved on back.
  - Silver medal, 1907; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Silver with a man throwing, "Jamestown Exposition College Championship 1907" engraved on front; "100 Yds Dash" engraved on back.
  - Silver medal, 1932 May 7; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Silver and oval. "Princeton Harvard Dual Track and Field Meet." "120 Yds. High Hurdles May 7, 1932" on reverse.
  - Silver medal, 1929; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Silver and round with "Pennsylvania Princeton Freshman Dual Meet" "Low 220 Yds. Hurdle 1929" on reverse.
  - Silver medal, 1931; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Silver and irregularly shaped with "Cornell University Dual Meet." "Princeton High 129 Yds. Hurdle 1931" on reverse.
  - Silver medal, 1932; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Silver and round with "Princeton-Yale University Track AA." "120 YD. High Hurdles 1932" on reverse.
  - Silver medal, 1930; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Silver and round with "Princeton-Yale University Track AA." "120 YD. High Hurdles 1930" on reverse.
  - Silver medal, 1930; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Silver and round with "Princeton-Yale University Track AA." "Broad Jump 1930" on reverse.
  - Silver medal, 1929; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Silver and round with "Pennsylvania Princeton Freshman Dual Meet." "Run Broad Jump 1929" on reverse.
  - Track Medal, 1906; 1 box (Box E.18)
    AR.2009.021
    Bronze, 220 yard run, Caledonian Games, with orange and black ribbon; won by Eugene Tittman, Class of 1909.
  - Track Medal, 1906; 1 box (Box E.18)
    Gold, 220 yard run, P.U.T.T.A., Fall Games; with orange and black ribbon. Won by Eugene Tittman, Class of 1909.
  - Track Medal, 1906; 1 box (Box E.18)
    Bronze, 50 yard dash, 3rd Annual Indoor Track Meet, with orange and black ribbon. Won by Eugene Tittman, Class of 1909.
  - Track Medal, 1906; 1 box (Box E.18)
    Silver, 100 yard run, P.U.T.T.A., Fall Games; with orange and black ribbon. Won by Eugene Tittman, Class of 1909.
  - Track Medal, 1906; 1 box (Box E.18)
    Gold,1 Mile Relay, P.U.T.T.A., Caledonian Games; with orange and black ribbon. Won by Eugene Tittman, Class of 1909.
  - Track Medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.18)
    Gold, 300 yard run, Annual Indoor Games, with orange and black ribbon.
  - Track Medal, 1907; 1 box (Box E.18)
    Bronze, 440 yard run, Princeton-Yale Track A.A.; with blue, orange and black ribbon. Won by Eugene Tittman, Class of 1909.
  - Track Medal, 1907; 1 box (Box E.18)
    Bronze, 220 yard dash, P.U.T.T.A., Caledonian Games; with orange and black ribbon. Won by Eugene Tittman, Class of 1909.
  - Track Medal, 1907; 1 box (Box E.18)
    Bronze, 440 yard run, P.U.T.T.A., Caledonian Games; with orange and black ribbon. Won by Eugene Tittman, Class of 1909.
  - Triennial Reunion pin, 1897; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Orange and round, "'94" in black; black ribbon with "Triennial Reunion June 1897" stamped on it, gold pin.
  - Watch key, 1823; 1 box (Box E.12)
    Cliosophic Society watch key. "Datum A Soc. Clio. Col. N. Caes. Kal. Oct. MDCCCXXIII" inscribed.
    EX4971
    Gift of George S. Heyer, Jr., '52.
  - Watch key, 1821; 1 box (Box E.12)
    EX2223
    Cliosophic Society watch key. "Alexander Aikman; Datum A Soc. Clio. Col. N. Caes. Ivo. Kal. Oct. MDCCCXXI" inscribed.
  - Watch key, 1821; 1 box (Box E.12)
    Cliosophic Society watch key. "J.W.L. Wager; Datum A Soc. Clio. Col. N. Caes. Ivo. Kal. Oct. MDCCCXXI" inscribed.
    EX4144
    Presented by Noah H. Swayne.
  - Watch key, 1814; 1 box (Box E.12)
    EX4273
    Cliosophic Society watch key. "M. B. Williams; Datum A Soc. Clio.Col.N.Caes.Ivo.Kal.Oct. MDCCCXIV" inscribed.
  - Watch key, 1812; 1 box (Box E.12)
    Cliosophic Society watch key. "C. Gilersleeve; and Datum A Soc.Clio ColN.Caes Io.Kal.Oct MDCCCXII" inscribed.
    EX4808
    Presented by Madeline N. Bradury.
  - Whig pendant, 1873; 1 box (Box E.12)
    EX5016
    "A" on front. "Whig Hall 1873" on back and Greek inscription.
- Series 9: Miscellaneous, 1701-2011; 56 boxes; 11 items
  This series contains a number of Princeton-related items, such as platters, portraits, and jewelry.
  - American flag with 48 stars, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.16)
    Was hung in the Faculty Room in Nassau Hall.
  - Anniversary Campaign Award, 2000; 1 box (Box Z.15)
    Edward C. Eisenhart '42.
  - Anniversary Campaign pen and pencil, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.14)
    "With One Accord"
  - Artifact, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    EX4365
    Indian arrow head. White stone.
  - Ashtray, Undated; 1 box (Box 17)
    AR.2004.059
    Silver ashtray with "P" in the middle and "Princeton University" around the edges.
  - Award, 1955-1956; 1 box (Box 21)
    Framed note of gratitude to Arthur J. Horton '42 for Annual Giving Campaign 1955-1956
  - Baton, Undated; 1 box (Box 14)
    Wooden conducting baton
  - Baton, Undated; 1 box (Box 14)
    Black conducting baton with silver tips labeled "Princeton Glee Club."
  - Baton, Undated; 1 box (Box 14)
    Metal baton and case. Silver label "To Walter Nollner in honor of 25 years as conductor of the Princeton University Glee Club."
  - Black and Orange umbrella hat, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.14)
  - Book mark clip, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.14)
    Gold P.
  - Box, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.10)
    Wooden black-balling box.
  - Branch, Undated; 1 box (Box D-Open (under stairs))
    Branch from tree. Reddish-brown leaves. Gold case with glass.
  - Bronze coins, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.7)
    Coins of Princeton signers (of the Declaration of Independence?). Richard Stockton, Benjamin Rush, John Witherspoon.
  - Buttons, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    Silver with "'16."
  - Buttons, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    Buttons or badges. Black with "'16" in silver (2)
  - Calling card plate, 1840-1880; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    EX4794
    Bronze and rectangular, "Prof. Stephen Alexander" engraved in mirror image.
  - Campus Permit, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.2)
    Driving permit? Metal seal with bolt and wing nut.
  - Cane, circa 1801-1900; 1 box (Box Z.12)
    Painted orange.
  - Cane, circa 1875; 1 box (Box Z.12)
    EX4270
    "Charles Herr and Princeton College" on handle. Signatures.
    Class of 1875
  - Cane, circa 1873; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    EX4420
    Ivory handle. "73" "Princeton College" "WW Van Valzah Lewisburg PA"
  - Cane, 1868; 1 box (Box Z.12)
    Cane with metal plate reading "From timber taken from US Constitution 1868 Otis Flagg Presbrey"
  - Cane, circa 1801-1900; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    EX4764
    "H Cox and Illinois" on handle. Signatures.
  - Cane, circa 1801-1900; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    Cane with signatures.
  - Cane, circa 1872; 1 box (Box Z.11)
    wood. "McClintock 72" on handle. Name of fraternity(?) below.
    Class of 1872
    McClintock
  - Cane, circa 1870; 1 box (Box Z.11)
    "Fendall, Tom Brown, esse quam vidr ri and '70' " on handle along with other signatures below.
    Tom Brown
  - Cane, circa 1876; 1 box (Box Z.11)
    "Faculty and class roll names and 1876."
  - Cane, circa 1801-1900; 1 box (Box Z.11)
    "Prishriy?" With signatures.
  - Cane, 1935; 1 box (Box Z.11)
    Painted black and orange. "69th Annual Cane Spree 1939 vs 1938 Nov 6 1935."
    Class of 1938, 1939
  - Cane, circa 1896; 1 box (Box Z.11)
    Plain brown with metal letters and numbers "P.C. and 96" attached.
  - Cane, circa 1863; 1 box (Box Z.11)
    EX4148
    "T. Sutphen?" "Class of '63" "Nassau Hall" and signatures. Metal band.
    Class of 1863
  - Cane, circa 1892; 1 box (Box Z.11)
    Silver plated handle with "P C '94". "W.L.C. Willkie Collins 92" scratched on silver.
    Class of 1892, 1894
  - Cane, circa 1801-1900; 1 box (Box Z.11)
    EX4864
    "C.N.C." and signatures.
  - Cane, circa 1801-1900; 1 box (Box Z.12)
    Thin with alligator carved on handle.
  - Cane, circa 1863; 1 box (Box Z.12)
    EX4143
    "H. Smythe and Nassau Hall Class 63" on handle.
  - Cane, circa 1875; 1 box (Box Z.12)
    with "E.F.W. and Nassau Hall 75" on handle and signatures.
  - Cane, circa 1870; 1 box (Box Z.12)
    with F.A.W.S. and Princeton College, NJ and "70" on handle with signatures.
  - Cane, circa 1876; 1 box (Box Z.12)
    with silver handle with "John S. Duffield" "Prodesse quam Conspici."
  - Cane, circa 1851; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    Silver Capped with "Princeton College Class 1851 from F.R. Harbaugh" "Log College 1726."
    Class of 1851
  - Cane, circa 1873; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    Ivory handle with "73".
  - Cane, circa 1801-1900; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    Very thin with top carved into man's head with very big nose.
  - Cane, circa 1801-1900; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    Knobby piece of wood with signatures.
  - Cane, circa 1801-1900; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    EX4142
    with signatures.
  - Cane, circa 1864; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    EX4269
    Ivory handle. "Theo F. Sanscay Princeton College Class 64" and signatures.
  - Cane, circa 1867; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    EX4296
    Metal plate "Joseph Creed Stamps." Signatures colored black and red.
    Class of 1867
  - Cane, circa 1863; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    EX4302
    "Toadvine and Nassau Hall" on handle. Signatures.
  - Cane, circa 1860; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    EX4597
    "W Helm" on handle in blue. Signatures. Long metal band about 3/4 down.
    Class of 1860
  - Cane, 1991-1992; 1 item (Item Bag.8)
    Wood with orange and black tassel. Letter describing workmanship included.
    Given by Annual Giving office to Ben Primer.
  - Cane, circa 1873; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    Ivory handle with "Princeton College" and "73"
  - Cane, circa 1879; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    Belonged to Andrew Allen Chambers Class of 1879
  - Cane, circa 1874; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    with signatures and "Class of 1874." Two nameplates on handle, "Joseph Parker, Jr., June 20th 1873" and "Frank T. Gorman, June 9, 1979"
    AR2000.016
  - Cane, 1873; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    Wood with signatures. "73" carved on end of handle. Portion of carving of human figure toward handle.
  - Cane, circa 1858-1861; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    AR.2005.066
    Owned by George Vansyckel Forman, Class of 1861.
  - Cane with bone handle, 1800; 1 box (Box Z.12)
    Signatures.
  - Cane with crooked handle, circa 1873; 1 box (Box Z.12)
    EX1430
  - Card, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    Valentine's greetings from Princeton University.
  - Card, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    "Mr. Woodrow Wilson. Princeton, NJ"
    Given by R. Cullinane '70 on 7/2/73
  - Cardboard panel, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    Reunions. 1906. Bookmark?
  - Cards, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    Dual pack. Princeton orange and black.
    Anonymous gift in memory of Charles W Millard, Jr. '26. 1989
  - Class directory, 1972; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    Reunions. 1972 directory of class of 1928.
  - Cocktail napkin or doily., circa 1930; 1 box (Box Z.17)
    AR.2001.054
    Picture of East Pyne old library on it, and note explaining its history.
  - Coin, 1998 September 19; 1 box (Box Z.14)
    Princeton University Stadium commemorative coin.
  - Coin collection can, 1963; 1 box (Box Z.2)
    Reunions. 1938's 25th in 1963. Orange.
  - Dance card, 1884 June 17; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    Covered with orange and black ribbon. "Princeton Sophomore Reception June 17, 1884."
  - Decal, circa 1946; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    Penn mascot standing on tiger.
  - Desk calendar, 1984; 1 box (Box Z.2)
    '94 with plaster tiger.
  - Dollar bills, 1973, 1999; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    AR.2000.029
    Two framed dollar bills signed by George P. Shultz '42, with letter from Shultz.
  - Plates and drawings displayed at the World's Columbian Exhibition, 1893; 2 items
    Items were created by undergraduate students of the Department of Graphics of the John C. Green School of Science as part of a display by the College of New Jersey at the World's Columbian Exhibition.
    - Drawing by Logan Coleman *1896, 1893; 1 item (Item 4)
      Inscription at the back of the framed item reads: "Selected from regular course technical free-hand drawing preparatory to the illustration of scientific reseach, Department of Graphics. College of New Jersey, Princeton, NJ."
    - Drawing by William Henry Schoonmaker *1896, 1893; 1 item (Item 5)
      Inscription at the back of the framed item reads: "First year plates in Elementary Technical Drawing selected from work done in Regular course in the Dept. of Graphics, John C. Green School of Science Princeton Univ."
  - Drink coaster, 1971; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    Reunions. 1931's 40th in 1971. One duplicate.
  - Embroidered tiger, Undated; 1 box (Box 40)
    AR.2010.037
    "21" sewn on chest. Class of 1921?
  - Fabric swatch, circa 2004-2005; 1 box (Box 24)
    AR.2009.114
    Class of 1975. Reunion costume fabric swatch. Orange and black with "'75" logo and tiger.
  - Fabric swatch, circa 2004-2005; 1 box (Box 24)
    Reunion costume fabric swatch. White fabric with orange and black stripes.
  - Fabric swatch, circa 2004-2005; 1 box (Box 24)
    Class of 1969. Reunion costume fabric swatch. Orange and black yin yang pattern.
  - Fabric swatch, circa 2004-2005; 1 box (Box 24)
    Class of 1980. Reunion costume fabric swatch. Black fabric with Nassau Hall pattern.
  - Fabric swatch, circa 2004-2005; 1 box (Box 24)
    Class of 1981. Reunion costume fabric swatch. White fabric with black and orange "81" logo.
    Class of 1981
  - Fabric swatch, 2005; 1 box (Box 24)
    Class of 1995. 10th reunion costume fabric swatch. White and orange striped fabric.
  - Fan, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.5)
    Orange and black striped.
  - Fan, 1896; 1 box (Box Z.9)
    Princeton '96. Flower print with signatures.
  - Fan, circa 1891-1900; 1 box (Box Z.5)
    Blue print. "Rockwood" with various events and dates.
  - Fan, 1874; 1 box (Box Z.5)
    Wooden with drawings and signatures.
  - Fan, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.5)
    Ivory? With Princeton pennant.
  - Fob, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    EX4304
    Copper and with square centerpiece; engraved "S. Alexander December 05th 1776" on one side; Greek letters for Phi, Beta, Kappa engraved on the other.
  - Framed drawings, Undated; 1 item
    "Plates selected from the Regular course in Technical Freehand drawing preparatory to the Illustration of Scientific Research Dept. of Graphics, college of N.J."
  - Frisbee, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
    Orange frisbee. "University Health Services."
  - Full wine bottle, 1995; 1 box (Box Z.14)
    1994 Sonoma County Chardonnay. Specially labeled for Class of 1970's 25th reunion. Funny label on back.
  - Gavel, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.9)
    Wood. Made of wood from Nassau Hall??
  - Gavel, circa 1923; 1 box (Box Z.9)
    Wooden, with "'23" on ends and years 1919-1962 listed with names of students.
  - Geology school cards in frame., 1928; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    Invite and expedition card to "Miss Miller for one night only"
    Gift of Frederick Redpath, given on Oct 6, 1994.
  - Gold coin, 1939; 1 box (Box 11)
    35th reunion. "Princeton 1904"
  - Gold spike, 1969; 1 box (Box Z.9)
    depicting 100th anniversary of joining of Central and Union Pacific Railroads and of intercollegiate football.
  - Golf tees, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.14)
    Class of 1953.
  - Inkwell and stand., 1963; 1 box (Box Z.10)
    Blown by Physics Glassblowers. Metal stand with "Princeton".
    Given 1972 with note.
  - Jewelry, circa 1912; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    2 tiger claws of different sizes; gold setting for the larger one, silver setting for the smaller one, both mounted with "94" and engraved "Society of the Claw Princeton University"; "Howard C. Butler Archaeologist" engraved on the larger claw.
    EX4245
    H. C. Butler
  - Jewelry, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    Carved agate stone [carnelian]. Letter seal of John Maclean (1816). "JM Ubi Libertas, Ibi Patria" engraved.
    EX4286
    Gift of Henry E. Hale (1892), Sept. 19, 1935.
  - Jewelry, 1782; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    Oval and engraved with "V 1782." Silver button worn by Richard N. Venable at his Princeton graduation in 1782.
    EX4295
    Emma C. Venable
  - Jewelry, circa 1912; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    EX4410
    Tiger claw, with gold setting engraved "Society of the Claw Princeton University" on one side, "Franklin S. Spalding Educator" on the other.
  - Jewelry, 1889; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    EX4471
    Ring, with monogram "PTS" encased. "My mother's engagement ring Julia D. Smith" (Caption on the original case).
  - Jewelry, circa 1874; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    EX4796
    Sleeve link of coins. Unearthed near the Cannon.
  - Jewelry, circa 1891; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    Buttons and charm. 3 buttons, all engraved with "'91" over orange and black background; a clapper engraved "91."
    EX4857; EX4858
  - Jewelry, circa 1901; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    Pin "1901" Metal.
  - Jewelry, circa 1888; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    EX4791
    Ivy Club Pin 1888.
  - Jewelry, circa 1888; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    EX4790
    '88 pin.
  - Jewelry, circa 1888; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    Two '88 lapel buttons.
  - Jewelry, circa 1892; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    '92 lapel button.
  - Jewelry, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    Tie clip. With U seal.
  - Jewelry, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    Watch chain, with U seal.
  - Jewelry, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    Cuff links, with U seal.
  - Jewelry, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    Grad council pendants.
  - Jewelry, circa 1926; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    Lapel button. Class of 1926.
  - Jewelry, circa 1936; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    Lapel button. Class of 1936.
    EX4566
  - Jewelry, circa 1941; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    Lapel button. Class of 1941.
  - Jewelry, circa 1879; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    Lapel button. Class of 1879.
    EX4563
  - Jewelry, circa 1926; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    Cloister Inn pins. CWM initials.
    anon gift in memory of Charles W Millard, Jr. '26
  - Jewelry, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    OSS pin.
    Given to Luchet? '27 by Horton '42. Note attached.
  - Jewelry, circa 1900; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    Pendant. "I.O. of K. '99 to Jim Knowlton 1900"
    Given to Knowlton by "kidnappers" of sophomore class. They kept him from the cane spree. letter attached. Given by Knowlton's grandson, Thomas W. Wright '62
  - Jewelry, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    AR.1993.011
    Pin, U. seal with anchors around it.
  - Jewelry, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    AR.1994.075
    Pendant, "Princeton Pictorial", "KP Jr. '25" engraved on back.
  - Jewelry, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    AR.1996.062
    Cufflinks, painted with U. seal '35.
  - Jewelry, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    Lapel pin. Groundbreaking shovel with "79."
  - Jewelry, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    AR.2008.110
    Cuff links with tiger and lion motif.
  - Jewelry, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    Gold chain with Princeton pendants.
  - Jewelry, circa 1924; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    Gold pendant with tiger. Front: "Princeton Intra Collegiate Athletic Association"; Back: "Fencing, 1924-25 EPEE."
  - Key, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
    Nassau Hall ceremonial key in wooden box. Note in box suggests the key was made as a Bicentennial gift.
    Note in box suggesting that the key was the possession of J. Douglas Brown '19.
  - Key chain, 1985; 1 box (Box Z.2)
    Black with tiger.
  - Key chain, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.14)
    Tiger head key chain
  - Key chain, Undated; 1 box (Box 18)
    Gold key chain with "USS Princeton CG 59" engraved
  - Lampshade, circa 1960; 1 box (Box 46)
    Off-white paper lampshade adorned with ink drawing of Nassau Hall. Windows of Nassau Hall are pierced so that light can shine through.
    AR.2011.089
    Gift of Larry Sanford III '72
  - Lapel pin, circa 1879; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    "79" black and orange.
  - Lapel pin, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    Black with shield and "1935."
  - Lapel pin, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    Gold with shield and "1935."
  - Lapel pin, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    AR.2008.095
    Covered in orange and black fabric.
  - Large black wooden shield, Undated; 1 box (Box 22)
    with round brass Princeton plaque with shield and Princeton motto in the middle.
  - Laundry bag, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
    AR.2007.011
    University Laundry and Dry Cleaning bag. Orange bag with handwritten label "John McK. Bigelow." "41 Blair Hall."
  - Leather sewing kit, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.2)
  - License plate, 1956; 1 box (Box Z.6)
    "35 NJ"
  - License plate, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
    AR.2004.062
    New Jersey license plate "70 PEDE."
  - License plate, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
    New Jersey license plate "TIGER70." Class of 1970?
  - Lighter, Undated; 1 box (Box 17)
    Silver lighter with picture of tiger
    AR.2006.044
    Belonged to Henry Welsh Rogers, Class of 1896.
  - Linotype slugs, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.15)
    Princeton University Library. Assorted pieces from the old Princeton University Library Classed List.
  - Luggage tag, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    Leather with bronze tag reading "Princeton" on one side, "Penn. R.R." on other
  - Magnet, 1992; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    AR.2000.019
    White plastc rectangle with dinosaur, number 10, and "Oldnassaurus."
    Class of 1982
  - Magnet, 1995; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    White plastic square. "70's 25th" and image of loucust and seal.
  - Magnet, 1995; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    White rectangle. "Class of 1990's Fifth Reunion." Tiger in director's chair, calendar.
    Class of 1990
  - Magnet, 2011; 1 box (Box 24)
    AR.2010.029
    Class of 1956. 55th reunion. Small magnet.
  - Mandolin, circa 1900; 1 box (Box 29)
    "Princeton" on headstock, with strap and tassels
  - Mandolin, circa 1900; 1 box (Box 29)
    In case
  - Meal ticket, 1967; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    Reunions. 1927's 40th.
  - Medallion, circa 1929; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    Woodrow Wilson in profile. Plaster of Paris.
  - Menu card, 1884; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    Class of 1874 decennial reunion.